pauljrdesigns.com 2012-11-15

# Please check out the Paul Jr. privacy policy

**SECURE ORDERING**

Protecting your online order information at [http://www.pauljrdesigns.com](http://www.pauljrdesigns.com/) (“Paul Jr. Designs”) is very important to us. In our shopping checkout process, we use Secure Socket Layering (SSL), the industry-standard encryption technology that ensures the safety and security of your online order. When the letters "http" in the URL address change to "https," the "s" indicates you are in a secure area employing SSL.

Making a credit card purchase is just as safe on our web site as it is by telephone. But if you prefer to order merchandise from the website by phone, call toll-free 800-558-6440. Our customer service associates are available Monday through Friday, 8:00am - 5:00pm Eastern Time.

**PRIVACY POLICY**

At Paul Jr. Designs, we are committed to providing you the finest products along with excellent service. In order to accomplish this, we gather, use and share certain personal information. Our online privacy policy describes what we gather, with whom we share it, and how you may direct us not to share certain information with certain parties. Because the security of your personal information is very important to us, we restrict access to your nonpublic personal information to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We also maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect your nonpublic personal information.

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

Whenever you shop with Paul Jr. Designs we obtain from you the information we need to complete your transaction. This may include your name, address, telephone number, eMail address, and credit card number. We also retain details of your specific product purchases and transactions with us. If you register with us online, we may ask for additional information, such as your age, interests or product preferences. To improve our web site, we may collect non-personal information about how users navigate through the site.

**USE AND DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

We use the information we collect to process your purchase transactions, to send you marketing and promotional materials by mail or eMail, and to help us improve our store and online product assortments and services for you.

We may provide information we collect to third-party service providers that help us bring you our products and services, for example, a company that distributes our catalogs.

**CHANGES TO   THIS POLICY**

We may make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. We will communicate any such changes by updating this page, notifying you by eMail if you have registered your eMail address with us, or in writing, as required by law.

**CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act imposes certain requirements on web sites directed at children under 13 that collect information on those children, and on web sites that knowingly collect information on children under 13. Paul Jr. Designs is not directed at children under 13, and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under 13.

**LINKS TO OTHER SITES**

Paul Jr. Designs may contain links to web sites operated by other third parties. Paul Jr. Designs has no control over, or responsibility for, their content, information or activities, including security and use of personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies and terms of use of any third-party site before submitting any personal information.

**ONLINE ACCOUNT REGISTRATION**

Registering with Paul Jr. Designs will make your online shopping faster and easier. We can store your shipping addresses and billing information so that you don’t have to enter them each time you shop. You will also be able to save your shopping basket, check your order status, and review your order history. Your registered information will be securely stored with us, and you can add, delete, or change your registered information at any time using your password.

**EMAILS**

We may send promotional eMails to you only if you have asked to receive them. Each time you receive an eMail from us, you will be given the opportunity to "opt-out" or stop receiving them.
